stewmac.com 2016-12-04

# Privacy & Security | stewmac.com

Our online ordering is secured by the services of Norton Secured, powered by Symantec. 

## Privacy policy

Our privacy policy is simple: we do not share customer address or contact information with any other company. When you request a catalog or place an order with Stewart-MacDonald, rest assured we won't pass your name or contact information on to anyone else.

However, being a modern website, we do collect information from you in several different ways while you browse and shop. Like most eCommerce websites, our site employs cookies and web beacons to speed your navigation of the website, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your website usage.

  * **Cookies** are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from websites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of the website. Cookies do not and cannot infiltrate your hard drive or access a User's confidential information; our cookies are not "spyware."
  * **Web beacons** assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a web page on the website has been viewed and, if so, how many times. For example, any electronic image on the website, such as a product image, can function as a web beacon.

Stewart-MacDonald uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the stewmac.com website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt-out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), or [permanently using a browser plugin](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

As is true of most websites, the website server automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access the website. We may also log your Internet Protocol, or IP address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing, and system troubleshooting purposes.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. We will not share this phone number with any third parties (outside of our payment processors: PaymenTech and PayPal) unless permission is explicitly granted.

You may choose to submit a product review on product pages. If you choose to do so, we will ask for your email address and geographic location. If you submit a review, your geographic location will be visible to other users (your email address will be kept private). Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the website. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review or comment without disclosing any personal information.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt-out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

Upon your request, we will (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emails to your email address; and/or (c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests simply by contacting us.

Upon request we may provide website visitors with access to all information that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password), transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases), and communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our website (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries).

With respect to security; we have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our website.

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on the website so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us.

The bottom line: Feel secure shopping for guitar tools, parts, and supplies from Stewart-MacDonald.
